<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on DevOps 059</title>
    <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-059-advanced/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on DevOps 059</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:01:55 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-059-advanced/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What I learned from this course</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-059-advanced/posts/bp2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:01:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-059-advanced/posts/bp2/</guid>
      <description>CS-EJ4101 Introduction to DevOps 059 Learned Too early to say what I have learned but few things below.
 Have been using GitHub but never used the github pages so learned how to use it. Learned the basics of DevOps thru&amp;rsquo; the online course link provided.  Learning is never ending. Ok, having said that now go grab coffee and begin conversation with friends. Share new ideas and make try make complex things simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I took this course</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-059-advanced/posts/bp1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:01:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-059-advanced/posts/bp1/</guid>
      <description>CS-EJ4101 Introduction to DevOps 059 Here are few points why I took this course
 Trying to grasp the knowledge of what DevOps actually is as it is being implemented in almost each and every organizations these days. Learn the continuous deployment technique to make things easier To know if DevOps is for me or not Why automating tasks can help in solving the problems To learn the DevOps culture To know the Traditional versus DevOps software Development Life Cycle To gain knowledge of the most important technologies and software used in DevOps Know the insights of cloud technologies and how it can help in our day to day life  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>